This is a big job.
这是个大工程.
But we can do it.
但是我们能做好.
Klara Kovak, here we come.
Klara Kovak,我们来了.
Nancy, Yvonne. Do come in.
Nancy,Yvonne.请进.
It's nice, but it's not quite right.
这房子装修得挺好,但是感觉不对.
We've had several decorators come in,
我们请了几位装潢师,
but so far, it's been a disappointment.
但到目前为止, 结果还是令人失望.
Notice the colors.
注意下颜色.
They simply won't do.
根本不行.
I can't bear to look at them...
我简直无法忍受去看他们...
Antonio and I hired a firm to fix the walls.
Antonio和我雇了个公司来修理墙壁.
Well, we came home to find the kitchen completely ruined.
Well,我们回家后发现厨房彻底给毁了.
Do you know what they said to me?
你知道他们对我说什么吗?
From then on,
从那时起,
I watched the workmen do every little thing,
我看着那些工人们做每件活儿,
no matter how small.
无论多么小的事.
After all, how else will I know...
不然的话,我怎么知道...
And look at this carpet.
瞧着地毯.
I don't like carpets.
我不喜欢地毯.
You see people covering beautiful wood floors.
你看人们把漂亮的木地板盖住.
It makes no sense whatsoever...
这简直没有道理...
I'll have the architect send you the plans.
我会叫建筑师给你们拿图纸来.
-Ms.Kovak   -Oh, Klara.
-Kovak女士  -Oh,叫我Klara好了.
Klara.
I'm sorry. I thought the phone was off.
对不起.我以为手机关了.
Excuse me.
失陪一下.
As I was saying...
正如我刚才所说的...
Hello. Hi.
喂.你好.
I'm in a meeting, but keep talking.
我正在开会,不过你接着说吧.
I need the break.
我正需要休息一下.
What's up? Who?
发生什么事了?谁?
She asked you what?
她让你做什么?
What did you say?
你怎么说的?
Wow. OK, honey. I'll see you tonight.
Wow.好,亲爱的.我们晚上见.
We'd love you to come to our office.
非常欢迎你来我们办公室.
We'll call and arrange an appointment.
我们会打电话约时间的.
Wow.
What were we doing in there?
我们刚才在那里干什么?
That house is fine.
那房子已经很好了.
What did Klara say?
Klara是怎么说的?
"It's nice but it's not quite right."
"挺好的,但感觉不对."
She wants us to make it right!
她想让我们把它弄对!
Oh no!
Oh 不!